Guide to the Robert W. Clower Papers, 1920s-2000 RL.00235
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Robert W. Clower papers
1920s-2000
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Clower, Robert W.
RL.00235
20 Linear Feet 11 boxes.
1 Megabytes One set.
Robert Clower (1926-2011) was the Hugh C. Lane Professor of Economic Theory, Emeritus at the University of South Carolina. This collection primarily documents his professional life through his correspondence, writings, research, teaching, and professional activities. It forms part of the Economists' Papers Archive.
Conditions Governing Access
Access note. Some materials are electronic records that require special equipment. Contact Research Services with questions.
Conditions Governing Access
Access note. Some materials are fragile audiovisual/photographic formats that may need to be reformatted before use. Contact Research Services for access.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Robert W. Clower papers were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book and Manuscript Library as gifts from Clower between 1992-2001 and Virginia Weathers in 2014.
Arrangement
The Robert W. Clower papers are arranged into seven series: Writings, Teaching, Legal, Professional, Personal, Research, and Correspondence.
Biographical / Historical
1926, Feb. 13 Born in Pullman, WA; son of F. W. Clower (Professor of Economics at Washington State University) and Mary V. Clower
1943 Graduated from Pullman High School; 52 out of 54 on academic honors list
1943 Joined US Army; 31 months of service
1946, Jan. 7 Married Frances Hepburn (of Aberdeen, Scotland) in Wiesbaden, Germany
1946, Summer Returned to the US and enrolled at Washington State University
1948, Apr. F. W. Clower died
1948 Graduated with BA in economics, summa cum laude, from Washington State University; elected Phi Beta Kappa, Phi Kappa Phi scholastic honors; began teaching at Washington State in senior year following death of his father
1948-1949 MA, Economics, Washington State University
1949-1952 Took up residence in Oxford as Rhodes Scholar, where he researched under John R. Hicks; earned Bachelor of Letter, Economics, Oxford University, 1952
1950-1952 Assistant Tutor, New College, Oxford
1952-1957 Assistant Professor of Economics, Washington State University
1954, July (with D. W. Bushaw) "Price Determination in a Stock-Flow Economy," Economometrica
1957 (with D. W. Bushaw) Introduction to Mathematical Economics
1958-1964 Chair, Department of Economics, Northwestern University
1960, Oct. (with M. L. Burstein) "On the Invariance of the Demand for Cash and Other Assets," Review of Economic Studies,
1961-1962 Director, Economic Survey of Liberia
1963-1966 Editorial Board, The American Economic Review
1965 "The Keynesian Counter-Revolution: A Theoretical Appraisal," The Theory of Interest Rates
1966 Growth Without Development, an Economic Survey of Liberia
1967, Dec. "A Reconsideration of the Microfoundations of Monetary Theory," Western Economic Journal
1968-1969 Dean, School of Social Studies and Professor of Economics, University of Essex
1971-1986 Professor of Economics, University of California, Los Angeles
1972 (with J. F. Due) Microeconomics
1973-1980 Managing Editor, Economic Inquiry
1976 Legally separated from Frances (Hepburn) Clower
1978 Honorary Fellow, Brasenose College, Oxford
1979? Married Georgene Thousandfriend
1981-1985 Managing Editor, The American Economic Review
1985, Spring Benedict Distinguished Visiting Professor, Carleton College
1986-2000 Hugh C. Lane Professor of Economic Theory, University of South Carolina
2011, May 2 Died in South Carolina
Scope and Contents
This collections consists of professional correspondence, writings, teaching material, research files, and some personal and legal materials from Clower's career, which stretched from 1949-1999.
His correspondence includes many prominent names of 20th century economics: Milton Friedman, John R. Hicks, Peter Howitt, Arjo Klamer, David Laidler, Axel Leijonhufvud, Don Patinkin, Joan Robinson, Paul Samuelson, and others. Duke University faculty are represented by Craufurd Goodwin, Neil DeMarchi, and Roy Weintraub. Also included are Moses Abramowitz, Jess Benhabib, Clive Bull, David Colander, Paul Davidson, Frank Hahn, John Haltiwanger, Tom Hazlett, Roger Kormendi, Larry Kotlikoff, Robert Solow, and Sir Alan Walters.
The collection also includes manuscript files of Clower's writings, ranging from notes and fragments to drafts and copies of published articles. Topics include monetary theory, price theory, price determination, employment, banking, disequilibrium, stock-flow analysis, Keynesian economics/macroeconomics, Say's Law, and mathematical economics. Many of the writings are untitled typescripts and fragments of notes.
In addition, the collection includes writings from Clower's father, F. W. (Fay Walter) Clower, also an economist; two copies of John Maynard Keynes's The General Theory of Employment Interest and Money, annotated by Clower; six audiocassettes with dictated letters; teaching material from several classes taught by Clower throughout his career; and legal transcripts of 1979 court cases and hearings in which he testified.
Banking; Employment; Economics -- Study and teaching -- United States; Economists -- United States -- Correspondence; Equilibrium (Economics); Keynesian economics; Monetary policy; Pricing; Say's Law; Clower, Robert W.; Economists' Papers Archive; Friedman, Milton, 1912-2006; Hicks, John, 1904-1989; Howitt, Peter; Leijonhufvud, Axel; Patinkin, Don; University of California, Los Angeles. Department of Economics -- Faculty; University of South Carolina -- Faculty
- Writings, 1948-1999; 1
  Conditions Governing Access
  Access note. Some materials are electronic records that require special equipment. Contact Research Services with questions.
  Scope and Contents
  Includes notes, fragments, drafts, and copies of published articles. Also includes Clower's book chapters and reviews, public lectures, and responses to other authors. Some of the titles include accompanying correspondence and edits by Clower and his collaborators. Arranged alphabetically by title, with untitled and loose excerpts are at the end.
  - An American Program for World Peace in the Present Crisis, 1948 (Box 1)
    Scope and Contents note
    Draft of essay for Tamiment Social and Economic Institute contest.
  - The Analogy Between Ordinary and Relative Reference Analysis, undated (Box 1)
    Typed draft.
  - The Anatomy of Competitive Pricing, undated (Box 1)
    Handwritten draft excerpt.
  - The Anatomy of Economics, undated (Box 1)
    Drafts of chapter abstracts.
  - The Anatomy of Monetary Theory, 1977 (Box 1)
    Offprint and typed drafts.
  - Are Administered Prices Socially Undesireable?, undated (Box 1)
    Offprint.
  - The Art of Economics, undated (Box 1)
    Preface and introduction drafts.
  - Article and book reviews by Robert Clower, undated (Box 1)
    Various reviews written by Clower about other authors' work.
  - The Asset Portfolio Decision - Corporate Profits Dividends and Retained Earnings, undated (Box 1)
    Handwritten draft and models.
  - Axiomatics in Economics, 1994 (Box 1)
  - Barter Exchange and Monetary Theory, undated (Box 1)
  - Basic Topics in Economics, undated (Box 1)
    Outline of book.
  - A Bayesian Approach to the Pricing Policy of an Ignorant Trader, 1973 (Box 1)
    Draft and notes.
  - Business Enterprise and Economic Change: Essays in Honor of Harold F. Williamson, 1974 (Box 1)
    Review of Clower's contribution.
  - Business Investment and the Theory of Price, undated (Box 1)
    Published pages.
  - Capitalist Production in a Stationary State, undated (Box 1)
    Typed and handwritten draft excerpts.
  - Causal Systems and Stability, 1965 (Box 1)
  - Causal Systems in Macroeconomic Theory, undated (Box 1)
    Typed excerpt with annotations.
  - Class assignments, Econ. 300, undated (Box 1)
    Clower's school papers.
  - The Classics and Keynes: A Reinterpretation, 1958 (Box 1)
  - Comment on Benevie: Choice Theoretic Basis for Disequilibrium Models, undated (Box 1)
  - Comment on "On the Behavioral and Rational Foundations of Economic Dynamics", 1986 (Box 1)
    Photocopy of published pages.
  - Comment: The Optimal Growth Rate of Money, undated (Box 1)
    Offprints.
  - Comment: Perspectives on Twentieth Century Economic Theory, 1971-1973 (Box 1)
    Typed draft and photocopies.
  - The Common Sense of Markets and Money, undated (Box 1)
    Typed draft with annotation.
  - Competition, Monopoly, and the Theory of Price, 1955 (Box 1)
    Journal issue and offprint.
  - Continuing Crisis in Macroeconomics, undated (Box 1)
    Drafts of various versions.
  - Conversations with Leading Economists, by Howard Vane and Brian Snowden, 1998-1999 (Box 1)
    Transcript and correspondence.
  - The Coordination of Economic Activities, 1973-1976 (Box 1)
    Outline and drafts from the book.
  - The Coordination of Economic Activities: A Keynesian Perspective, 1975 (Box 1)
    Offprint of article.
  - Critical Essays in Economic Theory, 1999 (Box 1)
    Outlines.
  - The Dalton Swiss Movement Plan to Develop Liberia and End the Cold War, undated (Box 1)
    Carbon copy.
  - Demand Theory, undated (Box 1)
    Draft.
  - Determinants of Growth in Developed Countries, 1958 (Box 1)
    Lecture notes.
  - Discussion of "Current Implications of the Roosevelt Years," by Buchanan, 1979 (Box 1)
  - Disequalibrium Economics: A Critique of Contemporary Price Theory, undated (Box 1)
    Photocopied draft.
  - Dual Decision Hypothesis, 1995 (Box 1)
    Draft and references.
  - A Dynamical Model of Consumer Behavior (Chapter 5 Appendix), undated (Box 1)
  - Earning, Spending, Saving, and Lending, undated (Box 1)
  - Economic Policy as an Instrument of Foreign Policy, undated (Box 1)
  - Economics as a Science, undated (Box 1)
  - Economists and Society: Confessions of an Erstwhile Journal Editor, undated (Box 1)
    Speech with edits.
  - Effective Control Through Coherent Decentralization with Preemptive Goals, 1967 (Box 1)
  - Effective Demand Failures: Another Perspective, 1973 (Box 1)
    Original article (by Herschel Grossman) and Clower's response, drafts.
  - The Emergence of Economic Organization, 1998-2000 (Box 1)
    Draft, copies.
  - Empirical Analysis of American Economic Development with Special Reference to the Great Depression, 1869-1896, 1964 (Box 1)
    NSF Proposal.
  - The End of Keynesian Economics?, undated (Box 1)
    Draft with edits.
  - Ends and Means in Disequilibrium Analysis, undated (Box 1)
    Drafts.
  - Ends and Means in Monetary Theory, undated (Box 1)
  - An Essay on the Empirical Implications of the Concept of Aggregate Study, 1949 (Box 1)
  - The Evolution of Money, Markets, and Firms, 1996 (Box 1)
    Drafts with edits, correspondence.
  - Financial Reform in New Zealand: A New Beginning?, 1984-1995 (Box 1)
    Copy and correspondence.
  - Foundation of Macroeconomic Analysis, 1967-1968 (Box 1)
    Draft, never published.
  - Foundations of Disequilibrium Analysis, undated (Box 1)
    Draft excerpt.
  - Foundations of Economics, 1992-1993 (Box 1)
  - Foundations of Monetary Theory, undated (Box 1)
    Handwritten draft.
  - The Foundations of Money Illusion in a Neoclassical Micro-Monetary Model: Comment, 1976 (Box 1)
  - A Framework for Monetary Analysis, undated (Box 1)
    Outline.
  - The Free Market: An Economic Analysis, undated (Box 1)
    Outline draft.
  - The Free Money Fable, undated (Box 1)
    Drafts with edits.
  - From Markets to Money, 1998-1999 (Box 1)
  - Fundamentals in the Development of the Labor Movement in Japan to 1930, 1954 (Box 1)
  - Fundamentals in the Development of the Labor Movement in Russia, 1954 (Box 1)
  - The Future of Banking in Pakistan, 1955 (Box 1)
    Photocopy of published article.
  - The General Theory: What's it all about?, undated (Box 1)
  - The General Theory of Competitive Price, 1950-1951 (Box 1)
  - The General Theory, 2nd Edition, 1992-1994 (Box 1)
    Drafts, correspondence.
  - The Genesis and Control of Inflation, 1979 (Box 1)
  - Growth without Development: An Economic Study of Liberia, 1966 (Box 1)
  - Heuristic Analysis of the Continuing Crisis of Keynesian Economics, 1987 (Box 1)
    Transcript.
  - Hicks' Theory of Markets: What's Next?, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Household Choice: The Dual Decision Hypothesis, undated (Box 1)
  - The Ideas of Economists, 1972 (Box 1)
    Draft and photocopy of published chapter.
  - Income and Prices: A Reconsideration of the Microfoundations of Macroeconomics, undated (Box 1)
  - Income, Wealth, and the Theory of Consumption, 1967 (Box 1)
    Research grant application.
  - Inductive Inference and Business Behavior, 1959 (Box 1)
    Draft of conference paper.
  - Inflation: Sense and Nonsense, undated (Box 1)
  - Introduction to Economic Theory and its Applications, undated (Box 1)
  - Introduction to Mathematical Economics, 1957 (Box 1)
    Typescript of book.
  - The Invisible Hand, 1991 (Box 1)
  - Is there an Optimal Money Supply?, 1970 (Box 1)
  - Keynes and the Classics: A Millenial Retrospect, 1997 (Box 1)
  - Keynes and General Equilibrium Analysis: A Critique of Contemporary Price Theory, undated (Box 1)
  - Keynesian, Classical, and Stock-Flow Analysis, undated (Box 1)
  - The Keynesian Counter-Revolution: A Theoretical Approach, 1979 (Box 1)
  - The Keynesian Cross Revisited, 1986 (Box 1)
  - The Keynesian Debate, undated (Box 1)
    Introduction draft.
  - Keynesian Economics: Postscript, 1996 (Box 2)
  - The Keynesian Paradigm: An Attempt at Reconstruction, 1971 (Box 2)
  - The Keynesian Revolution: Another Assessment, undated (Box 2)
  - The Keynesian Revolution: Reflections on Some Loose Ends, undated (Box 2)
    Photocopy of draft with edits.
  - The Last of the Classical Economists, 1993 (Box 2)
  - Letter to the Editor of London Daily Times, 1949 (Box 2)
    Robert Clower's first publication.
  - The Liberian Banking System, 1962 (Box 2)
    Letter to Professor Letiche.
  - The Logistics of Exchange, undated (Box 2)
    Abstract.
  - Macroeconomics and the Competitive Struggle, undated (Box 2)
  - Madmen and Economists, undated (Box 2)
  - Mainsprings of African Economic Progress, 1966 (Box 2)
    Pamphlet.
  - Market Economies: Evolution, Coordination, and Control, 1997 (Box 2)
  - Market Mechanisms, undated (Box 2)
  - Marshall on Deposit Multipliers, 1975 (Box 2)
    Correspondence.
  - Mathematical Introduction to Price Theory, 1969 (Box 2)
    Drafts and excerpts of book.
  - Mathematics and Economics: The Contemporary Prospect, 1959-1989 (Box 2)
    Copy with annotations from 1989.
  - The Mechanism of Exchange, undated (Box 2)
    Draft of Chapter 2 (book unknown).
  - Microeconomics II: The Theory of Consumer Behavior, undated (Box 2)
    Draft of Chapter 6 (book unknown).
  - Monetary Economics, 1992 (Box 2)
    Draft of preface.
  - Monetary History and Positive Economics, 1964 (Box 2)
    Review of A Monetary History of the United States by Friedman and Schultz.
  - Monetary Theory book, 1966; 2 folders (Box 2)
    Drafts and notes.
  - Monetary Theory book, reissue, 1983 (Box 2)
    Correspondence and outline.
  - Monetary Theory and Macroeconomics: A Perspective, undated (Box 2)
    Draft and offprint.
  - Money and Markets, undated (Box 2)
    Afterword of book.
  - Money and the Theory of Value, undated (Box 2)
  - Money, Credit, and the Timing of Transactions, 1976 (Box 2)
    Working paper.
  - Money, Growth, and Social Welfare, undated (Box 2)
  - Money, Markets, and Coase, 1992-1993 (Box 2)
  - Money, Markets, and Coase Electronic Files, 1986-1994; 5 files; less than 1 megabyte. (Digital-materials RL00235-SET-0001, Folder 1, Disk RL00235-FL5-0001)
    Text files.
  - Mr. Graaf's Producer-Consumer Theory: A Restatement and Correction, undated (Box 2)
  - "Mr. Keynes and the Classics" Revisited, 1986 (Box 2)
  - Monopolistic Competition and Price Determination, undated (Box 2)
    Draft with annotations.
  - New Microfoundations for the Theory of Economic Growth?, undated (Box 2)
  - Note on the Definition of Money and Related Concepts, undated (Box 2)
    Drafts, notes.
  - Oligopoly Theory: A Dynamical Approach, 1959 (Box 2)
    Journal issue.
  - On a Missing Chapter in Microeconomic Theory, undated (Box 2)
  - On Equilibrium and Stability in Macroeconomics, undated (Box 2)
  - On Rereading the General Theory, undated (Box 2)
    Handwritten drafts.
  - On the Existence of a General Theory of Price Determination, 1954-1955 (Box 2)
    Draft and rejection letter.
  - On the Invariance of Demand for Cash and Other Assets, undated (Box 2)
    Symposium publication.
  - On the Microdynamics of Price Formation in N-Seller Markets, 1956-1958 (Box 2)
    Photocopied drafts.
  - On the Pure Theory of Seller Competition, 1989; undated (Box 2)
  - On the Technology of Monetary Exchange, 1968; 1971 (Box 2)
  - On the Theory of a Money Economy, undated (Box 2)
    Draft excerpt with edits.
  - On the Theory of Market Equilibrium Where Sales Functions are Conjectural, undated (Box 2)
  - On Truth in Teaching Macroeconomics, 1991 (Box 2)
  - On-Site Preliminary Study of the Economy of Liberia Conducted by the Dept. of Economics of Northwestern University, 1960 (Box 2)
    Final report.
  - The Optimal Timing of Transactions, 1974-1976 (Box 2)
    Correspondence, notes.
  - The Optimality of Money Under Laissez Faire, undated (Box 2)
    Draft with annotations from 1999.
  - Permanent Income Hypothesis Reconsidered, undated (Box 2)
  - The Political Economy of Policy-Making, 1979 (Box 2)
    Foreword.
  - Post-Keynes Monetary and Financial Theory, 1999 (Box 2)
    Proofs and edits.
  - Pre-Keynesian Macroeconomics: The Marhsall Connection, 1987 (Box 2)
    Drafts and models.
  - The Present State of International Liquidity Theory, 1968 (Box 2)
  - Present State of Monetary Economics, undated (Box 2)
  - Price and Distribution Theory, 1958-1960 (Box 2)
    Untitled book draft.
  - Price Determination: An Intermediate Analysis of Product and Factor Markets, 1959; 2 folders (Box 2)
    Drafts of book, one with comments.
  - Price Theory, undated (Box 2)
    Drafts, "false starts," notes.
  - Price Theory and Conjectural Interdependence, undated (Box 2)
  - Price-Quantity Estimates and the Unity of Economic Theory, undated (Box 2)
  - Pricing and Disequilibrium lectures, 1979 (Box 2)
    Drafts of lectures in Mexico.
  - Pricing and Disequilibrium book, undated; 3 folders (Box 2)
    Chapter drafts, notes.
  - Pricing and Disequilibritum: A Heuristic Approach, undated (Box 2)
    Photocopied draft with edits.
  - A Primer of Macroeconomic Theory, undated (Box 2)
  - Principles of Economics Dynamics, 1953 (Box 2)
  - "Principles of Economics" Review, undated (Box 2)
  - The Problem of Industrial Depression in the United States, undated (Box 2)
  - The Problem of Second Best and the Efficient Pricing of Electricity, 1981 (Box 3)
    Draft and published version.
  - Puerto Rican Shipping and the U.S. Maritime Laws: An Economic Analysis, 1965 (Box 3)
    Prepared for the Transportation Center at Northwestern University.
  - Pure Theory of Price Setting/Monopoly/Market Economy/etc., undated (Box 3)
  - Recent Developments in the Keynesian Counter-Revolution, 1973 (Box 3)
    Lecture outline.
  - A Reconsideration of the Microfoundations of Monetary Theory, 1967 (Box 3)
  - A Reconsideration of the Theory of Competitive Price, undated (Box 3)
  - Reflections on Science?and Economics, 1974 (Box 3)
  - Reflections on the Keynesian Perplex, 1975 (Box 3)
  - A Reformulation of the Theory of Industrial Pricing, undated (Box 3)
  - A Reformulation of the Pure Theory of Foreign Exchanges, undated (Box 3)
  - Reminiscences of Keynes, 1971 (Box 3)
  - A Reply [to Rakshit], 1965 (Box 3)
  - Role of Trade Credit and Inventories in the Generation of Cumulative Movements in Economic Activities, 1971 (Box 3)
    Research proposal.
  - The Savings and Wealth Relation, undated (Box 3)
  - Say's Law and All That, 1995 (Box 3)
  - Say's Principle: What it Means and What it Doesn't Mean, Parts 1 and 2, 1974; 2 folders (Box 3)
    Drafts, notes, photocopy of published versions.
  - Scientific Method, undated (Box 3)
  - Selected Papers by Robert Clower (edited by Elgar), 1993 (Box 3)
    Notes.
  - Snarks, Quarks, and Other Fictions, 1973; 1999 (Box 3)
    Offprint with annotations.
  - Some Views on University Education in Pakistan, undated (Box 3)
  - The State of Economics: Hopeless, but not Serious?, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Statistics and Development Policy Decisions, 1962 (Box 3)
  - Stock and Flow Quantities: A Common Fallacy, 1959 (Box 3)
  - Stock-Flow Analysis, 1980 (Box 3)
  - Structural Unemployment and Inflation, undated (Box 3)
  - A Study of Elementary Learning and Response Mechanisms in Dynamical Monopoly Models, undated (Box 3)
  - A Suggestion for Generalizing the Pure Theory of Production, undated (Box 3)
  - A Synthesis of the Theories of Competitive and Non-competitive Price, undated (Box 3)
  - Theoretical Foundations of Monetary Policy, 1971 (Box 3)
    Photocopy of published chapter, with annotations.
  - A Theoretical Study of Seller Competition in an Organized Auction Market, undated (Box 3)
  - Theories of Capital Accumulation with Special Reference to their Ability to Explain the Experience of the U.S. since 1870, 1952; 2 folders (Box 3)
    Ph.D. thesis (2 copies)
  - Theory of Capital and Interest: A Restatement, undated (Box 3)
  - Theory of Monetary Economics, undated (Box 3)
  - Thinking Economically, 1968 (Box 3)
    Drafts and excerpts, with edits.
  - Towards a General Synthesis of Price Theory and Income Analysis, undated (Box 3)
    Drafts and excerpts.
  - Towards a General Theory of Disequilibrium Economics, undated (Box 3)
  - Towards a General Theory of Price Determination, 1954-1955 (Box 3)
  - Towards a Reconstruction of Economic Theory, 1993 (Box 3)
    Draft of address.
  - Towards a Unified Theory of Market Mechanisms, 1956 (Box 3)
    Draft of talk.
  - Trade Specialists and Money in an Ongoing Exchange Economy, 1982-1986 (Box 3)
    Drafts, correspondence, and photocopy of published version.
  - U.S. Trade Policy: Signs of Change?, 1978 (Box 3)
  - Views on University Education in Pakistan, 1955 (Box 3)
    Published version.
  - Vision of Adam Smith, undated (Box 3)
    Chapter draft for unknown book.
  - The Vision of J.M. Keynes, 1994 (Box 3)
  - Walras' Law writings, undated (Box 3)
    Drafts of articles, research relating to W.L.
  - Walrasian Equilibrium and the Distribution of Wealth, 1955 (Box 3)
    Draft, correspondence with Harry Johnson.
  - The Walrasian Paradigm and Monetary Economics, 1972 (Box 3)
    Draft with annotations from 1993.
  - What's Left of the General Theory?, undated (Box 3)
  - What Traditional Monetary Theory Really Wasn't, 1969 (Box 3)
  - What Went Wrong with IS-LM/AD-AS Analysis and Why? An Exercise in Back-Tracking, 1995 (Box 3)
  - Loose, untitled essays, drafts, pages, and calculations., undated; 2 folders (Box 3)
- Teaching, 1959-2000; 2
  Clower's syllabi, coursepacks, exams, and lecture notes from his tenure at Northwestern, UCLA, and the University of South Carolina. Arranged alphabetically by course code or title, with loose material on various topics at the end, along with special teaching engagements, such as Clower's Fulbright at the University of Siena and his Perugia Lectures series.
  - Econ A-12, 1958 (Box 4)
    Syllabus.
  - Econ B-01, 1968 (Box 4)
    Exams.
  - Econ B-02, 1968-1971 (Box 4)
  - Econ B-60: International Trade, 1962 (Box 4)
  - Econ C-08, 1968-1969 (Box 4)
  - Econ C-10: Intermediate Economic Theory for Graduates, 1964-1970 (Box 4)
    Syllabi, exams.
  - Econ C-11: Economic Theory: Income and Employment, 1966-1967 (Box 4)
  - Econ D-10, 1963-1967 (Box 4)
    Outline, exams.